President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of Abram Brubacher Records, 1904-1930; 2; 14.8
  - Soroities and Fraternities, 1930; 1933; 1939; Undated (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1930; 1933-1936; 1939; 1941 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Addresses etc. "Salary Adjustments", 1931 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Addresses etc. "Teacher Preparation", 1931 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Nursery Schools, 1931 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1931-1932 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Hawley Library - Library Conversion Plans, 1931-1932 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Speeches and Addresses, 1931-1933 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Temporary Emergency Relief, 1931-1933 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Horner, 1931-1934 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - H,I,J, 1931-1936 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Milne High School, programs, alumni, 1931-1936 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - K-L, 1931-1933 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Graduate Programs, Graduate Studies, 1931-1937 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Writings and Publications - Notes, Drafts, and Outlines, 1931; 1937 (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Writings and Publications, 1931-1937; Undated (Box 27 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - D, 1931-1938 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Simpson, A.D, Dr. Assistant Commissoner for Financial, 1931-1938 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate, 1931-1939 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - W, 1931-1939 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Addresses etc. "Problems of Social Reconstruction", 1932 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Departmental Reports - Summer Sessions, 1932 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - President Roosevelt, 1932 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - President's Report, 1932 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Publication - "The Teacher Goes to School", 1932 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Publication - "The Teacher - Training Program Re-Examined", 1932 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - S, 1932-1933 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1932-1933 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Commencement, 1932-1934 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - United States Department of Education, 1932-1934 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - G, 1932-1935 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Lape, Esther Everett, 1932-1935 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Educational Reports and Publications, 1932-1936 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Special Services Fee Fund, 1932-1938 (Box 28 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - American Council of Education, 1932-1940 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Residence Halls, 1932-1940 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Addresses etc. "The Prospects of American and Russian Youth", 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Addresses etc. "The Twentieth Century Teacher", 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Foundations Education Course - The Teacher's Personal Fitness for Teaching, 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Murals, 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Hicks, J Allen, 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Placement Data, 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Placement Data, 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - President's Annual Report, 1933 December (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - President's Report, 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Publications - "Social Values in Latin", 1933 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - President's Report, 1933-1934 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1933-1934 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Faculty State College, 1933-1935 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Scholarships - State, 1933-1935 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Sororities and Fraternities, 1933-1935 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Misc, 1933-1936 (Box 29 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Dean's List and Department of Education, 1933-1937 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Misc, 1933-1937 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Gideon Hawley Murals, 1933-1938 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Misc, 1933-1938 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Residence Halls, 1933-1938 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Certificates of Graduation, 1933; 1935; Undated (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Addresses etc. "Education for the new day", 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Addresses etc. "New York Education", 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Addresses etc. "Should a boy go to High School", 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Addresses etc. "What and How Much to Teach", 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File: Senior Class, 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Copeland, Royal Senator, 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Organizational Chart, 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Patry, Dr. Frederick, 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Placement Data, 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Publications - Review of "The Life and Works of Andrew Sloan Draper", 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Publication - "The Teacher of Today", 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Traffic Problems, 1934 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - President's Report, 1934-1935 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1934-1935 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Scholarships - State, 1934-1935 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Speeches and Addresses, 1934-1935 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Student Personal Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Sensitive Records, withdrawls, 1934-1936 (Box 30 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Spelman Fund, 1934-1936 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Auditor's Report (April 30, 1934-December 31, 1938), 1934-1938 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Collegiate Center, 1934-1938 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence File - P, 1934-1935; 1938 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence File - S Sigum Laudis, 1934-1938 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence File - U-V, University Club, 1934-1938 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - International Education, Fellowships in France, 1934-1938 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence File - K-L, 1934-1939 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Faculty appointments, Status, credentials, 1934-1939 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Financial Aid, Federal Aid, National Youth Administration-Aid, 1934-1939 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Speakers, 1934-1939 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Speakers, 1934-1939 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Student Christian Association, 1934-1939 (Box 31 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Summer Sessions, 1934; 1937-1939 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Cooper, Herman Dr. Assistant Commission of Education, 1934-1940 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Cooper, Herman Dr. Assistant Commission of Education, 1934-1940 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Extension Teaching, 1934-1940 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Addreses etc. "A Critical Period in American Education", 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Addresses etc. "Freedom and Security", 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Addresses etc. "The Teaching Impulse", 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - T, 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Faculty Assignements, 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Hidley Clarence Athletic Field Fund, 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Placement Data, 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Potter, Edward Eldred and Mrs. Lackey (sister), 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Time Card - Janitorial Staff, 1935 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - College Testing, 1935-1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Commercial Teachers and Commerce, 1935-1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Curriculum, 1935-1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Patriolism, Academic Freedom, 1935-1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - President's Report, 1935-1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - President's Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1935-1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Religious Education, 1935-1937 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Registration, 1935-1938 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - W, Convocation, 1935-1939 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - State Legislation - Appreciation, 1935; 1939 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1935-1936; 1939-1940 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Addresses etc. "The New Citizenship", 1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - American Association of Teacher's Colleges, 1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Appointment Bureau, 1936 (Box 32 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Association of Education Sororities, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Rejall, Honorary Degree, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Selective Admissions, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Seminar, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Sheats, Paul, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Social Studies, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Universities Scholarships, 1936 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Background (Annual Report), 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous - R, 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Myskania, 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Normal Schools and Teacher's Colleges, 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - President's Report, 1936-1937 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Cooper, Herman Dr. Assistant Commission of Education, 1936-1938 (Box 33 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Speeches and Addresses, 1936-1938 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Summer Session, 1936-1938 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence File - M-N, 1936-1939 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Regents Inquiry, 1936-1939 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Residence Halls, 1936-1939 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - American Association of Teacher's Colleges, 1936-1940 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Addresses etc. "A Formula For Citizenship", 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Addresses etc. "Education for Social and Civic Responsibility", 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Addresses etc. "Essential Character of the Instructional Staff", 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Addresses etc. "Problem of Citizenship", 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Career Bill, 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Placement Data, 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Placement Data, Miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Schoor, P., 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - State Education Department, 1937 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Department of Social Studies, 1937-1938 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1937-1938 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - President's Report, 1937-1938 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Report of Committee on Comprehensive Examinations, 1937-1938 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alumni Association, 1937; 1939 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Constitution Convention, 1937-1939 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Freshman Addresses, 1937; 1939 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File -V, 1937-1941 (Box 34 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Addresses etc. "Adult Education: Why and What?", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Addresses etc. "Do Secondary School Teachers Lack Adequete Preparation", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Addresses etc. "Essential Character of a Teachers College Instruction Staff", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Addresses etc. "The Full Measure of Devotion", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Addresses etc. "A Great Inheritance", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Addresses etc. "The Modern Languages in High School of Tomorrow", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Addresses etc. "Noblesse Oblige", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Addresses etc. "Public School and Political Purposes", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Addresses etc. "Public School and Political Purposes", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Addresses etc. "The Teacher of Teachers...", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Addresses etc. "What is Wrong with Our High Schools", 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Albany High Purchase, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - W, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - American College Yearbook, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Books by Faculty Members, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Committee A: Comprehensive Examinations, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Curriculum Changes, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Curriculum - Distribution, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Department Reports - Report of Dean, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Douglas, Gertrude E, Report of, 1938 February 26 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Emergency Peace Campaign, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Five Year Plea Curriculum, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Hatfield, Elliot Gymnasium, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Honor System, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Middle States Association, 1938 (Box 35 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - National Resources Committee, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - New York State Constitution, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Placement Data, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - "The Professional Education of Secondary School Teachers", 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Questionaire - (Self Analysis of Teaching Experience), 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Questionaires on Graduate Studies and Self analysis, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Report of the Liberal Arts Committee, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Report on the Professional Education of Secondary School Teachers, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Student Honor System, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Suspension Cases, 1938 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for teachers, 1938-1939 (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Albany Community Chart, 1938; Undated (Box 36 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Addresses etc. "An Educational Creed and Unfettered Teaching", 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Addresses etc. "Florence Nightingale Memorial", 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Addresses etc. "The Inquiry into Character and Cost of Education", 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Addresses, Magazines, Articles etc. "Social Competence", 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Addresses etc. "The Social World", 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Albany Academy, 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Broader Training for Administration, 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Memorial, 1939 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Imperial Policy Group, 1939-1940 (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Addresses etc. "The Accumulated Wisdom of the Ages", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Addresses etc. "College Students at Work on Student Affairs", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Addresses etc. "Education", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Addresses etc. "The Freshman Mind", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Addresses etc. "General Trends in Education", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Addresses etc. "The Great Moments of Insight", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Addresses etc. "Gregariousness and Collectivism", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Addresses etc. "Is Public Education Efficient?", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Addresses etc. "The New High School", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Addresses etc. "The New York State Teachers Association", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Addresses etc. "Professional or Professionalized", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Addresses etc. "Shall I go to College", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Addresses etc. "Social Reconstruction", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Addresses etc. "The Story", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Addresses etc. "Teaching a Technic Enthusiam", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Addresses etc. "The Teachers College Idea", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Addresses etc. "Teachers Meetings", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Addresses etc. "Teaching Citizenship", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Addresses etc. "Two Foundation Principles", Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Department of Education, Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Examination Questions, Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Library School, Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Richard, Leonerd W., Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Speeches, Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Student Grades, Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Teacher's Retirement, Undated (Box 37 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 35)
- Office of John M. Sayles, 1930-1950; 3; 4.67
  - A - Correspondence, 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1940-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albany Community War Chest aka Albany War Chest - Albany Victory War Chest, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative (closing of class controversy), 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Air Raid Procedure, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Day Speech, 1942; 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)